《地球百子》前情提要
Previously on "The 100"...
你真該在戰場上殺掉我
You should have killed me on that battlefield.
他很強悍
He's strong.
翻譯  pretty boy  喵球球  阿飄
■
如果我們想從這殺出條血路  就需要他
We need him if we're gonna fight our way out of here!
聽我說
Listen to me!
你是想報仇
Do you want your revenge,
還是想自己的同伴活下去
or do you want your people alive?
時間軸  風吹來的那片雲
校對  阿飄
拿著鑰匙  她會派支援來
Grab the keys. She's gonna send for reinforcements.
我們在找到一臺主機前
Until we find it a host,
後期  寶寶
沒有辦法阻止阿莉
we won't know how to stop Alie.
那我們就找一臺主機
Then let's find it a host.
只要我們找到露娜  一切都能結束
Once we find Luna, this'll be over.
總監  阿飄
安塔麗的謊言會被揭穿
Ontari'll be exposed as a fraud,
那個人工智能也會知道如何打敗阿莉
and the A.I. will tell us how to shut down Alie.
打開微信   掃瞄左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    美劇炸了
瞭解最新影視資訊字幕信息
那克拉克呢
What will you do with Clarke?
我會給她和其他人相同的選擇
I will give her the same choice as the rest.
露娜  你是最後一位夜之血脈
Luna, you're the last Nightblood.
你願意接受成為下一任司令嗎
Will you take it and become the next commander?
不
No.
現在怎麼辦
Now what?
車子的電差不多充滿了
Rover's almost charged.
我們得收拾東西趕快回去了
We need to pack up. We'll be home soon.
然後呢  逃跑嗎
Then what, run away?
我們不會逃跑  克拉克
We're not running away, Clarke.
我們要重新部署人員
We need to regroup with the others,
找到另一種辦法打敗...
and find another way to defeat--
沒有別的辦法
There is no other way.
我們得找到一名夜之血脈
We need to find a Nightblood.
我們要釋放火種
We need to unlock the flame.
只有這樣才能阻止阿莉
It's the only way to stop Alie.
你想要我們做什麼  克拉克
What do you expect us to do, Clarke,
隨便跑進哪個村莊
walk into random villages
問他們有沒有夜之血脈嗎
asking for their Nightbloods?
如果行  那就去做
If that's what it takes.
不  克拉克
No, Clarke.
如果阿莉能在露娜的船裡找到我們
If Alie can find us on Luna's rig,
那我們去任何地方都逃不過她的眼睛
then she can find us anywhere.
我不會幫你去毀掉
I won't help you destroy
另一個無辜的地表人村莊的
another innocent grounder village.
如果我們找不到夜之血脈
If we don't find a nightblood,
那任何地表人的村子都守不住
there won't be any grounder villages
我們也沒有任何地方可回
or a home for us to go back to.
正因如此  我們更應該回去
That's all the more reason we go there
確認我們的同伴沒事
and make sure our friends are ok.
她沒事的  讓她冷靜一下吧
She'll be fine. Just let her cool off.
對不起
I'm sorry.
把她和火種帶來給我
Bring her to me with the flame.
羅恩
Roan?
看來我不是唯一一個
Looks like I'm not the only one
跟著你的人
who's been following your tracks.
還給我
Give that back.
再見  瓦黑達
Good-bye, wanheda.
等等
Wait.
你該感謝我的
You have a real gratitude problem.
明白嗎
You know that?
你聽到我說話了嗎
Would you just hear me out?
我要找到一名夜之血脈接受火種
I need to find a nightblood to put that in.
我已經有夜之血脈要接受火種了
I already have a nightblood to put it in.
求求你住手
Please just stop.
因為你  安塔麗沒能正式登位
Because of you, Ontari never ascended,
所以不  我不會住手
so, no, I won't stop,
直到冰之國的司令登基
not until the Ice Nation has its commander.
你說什麼
You were saying?
把手放到我能看到的地方
Hands where I can see them.
你沒事吧
You ok?
沒事
Yeah.
走吧
Then let's go.
-他跟我們一起走  -怎麼可能
- He's coming with us. - The hell he is.
我為什麼要這麼做
Why would I do that?
因為我們目標一致
Because we both want the same thing--
把火种放入安塔麗體內
To put the flame in Ontari.
你怎麼知道他沒吞芯片
How do you know he's not chipped?
如果是  他怎麼會救我
If he were, do you think he would've saved me?
還是小心為妙
Still, we need to be sure.
現在可以了
Now we're sure.
《地球百子》
第三季  第十五集
鎖起來
Lock it up.
你們回來就好
Glad you made it back.
我們正擔心呢
We were getting worried.
露娜呢
Where's Luna?
露娜拒絕了
Luna said no.
他是誰
Who the hell is this?
冰之國的
He's Ice Nation.
更嚴格來說  是冰之國的國王
King of the Ice Nation, actually,
他能帶我們進波利斯
and he's our way into Polis.
走吧  殿下
Let's go, your highness.
你們兩個跟我一起
You two, on me.
我們去關押他
We'll take him to lockup.
-你想利用他接近安塔麗  -是的
- You want to use him to get to Ontari. - Yes.
他的手臂怎麼了
What happened to his arm?
貝拉米開槍打了他
Bellamy shot him.
能讓他合作  真是萬幸啊
Good luck getting him to cooperate.
你的手臂  我很抱歉
Sorry about your arm.
我們扯平了
Makes us even.
無論喜歡與否  我們需要彼此合作
Like it or not, we need each other.
有話直說吧  克拉克
Cut to the chase, Clarke.
你說我們目標一致
You said we wanted the same thing.
我要的是冰之國的司令
I want an Ice Nation commander.
而我可以用它給你這位
And I can give you one with this.
你明知道她要剿滅你們
And why would you do that
為什麼會這麼做呢
when you know she's vowed to wipe you out?
我們別無選擇
We don't have a choice.
這不僅是我們的戰爭
This isn't just our war.
我們面對的敵人
The enemy we're up against
不會放過任何人
is after everyone,
包括冰之國
including the Ice Nation.
唯一能阻止她的辦法就是得到火種裡的信息
The only way to stop her is to get the information off the flame,
唯一能辦到的辦法就是將它植入安塔麗的腦袋
and the only way to do that is to put it in Ontari's head.
冰之國無所畏懼
The Ice Nation isn't afraid.
你該畏懼
You should be.
這個東西並不在意你出自哪個部落
This thing doesn't care what clan you're from.
它會控制人心
It controls people,
它會像統治我們一樣
and it will take over the Ice Nation
統治冰之國
just like it took us over,
一個接一個  直到全部拿下
one person at a time until there is no one left.
它已經得到了安塔麗
It already has Ontari.
我在聽
I'm listening.
我們需要在她得到火種之前切斷她的聯結
We need to disconnect her before she gets the flame,
否則我們就是把阿莉要的東西拱手呈上
or we'll be giving Alie exactly what she wants.
要想做到  我們就得從一座
To do that, we have to abduct her from the center
遍佈上千思想相連  意志統一的人的
of a city filled with thousands of people
城市中心
who's minds are linked,
把她綁架出來
all of them thinking as one.
只要一人看到  所有人都看到
Whatever one sees, they all see.
只要一人聽見  所有人都聽見
Whatever one hears, they all hear.
我明白了
I get it.
我們何時動身
So when do we leave?
韋瑟山最好的催眠瓦斯
Knockout gas, Mount Weather's finest.
他們一把安塔麗帶出來
As soon as they bring Ontari out,
我們就把他們放倒
we put them to sleep.
棒
Nice.
因為她被植入了芯片  你們得
Because she's chipped, you'll have to emp her
在植入火種之前  像給我一樣給她電磁脈衝
like you did me before you give her the flame.
我以為亞哈毀了所有的手環
I thought Jaha destroyed all the wristbands.
他確實毀了  不過我回來了
So did he. Then I came home.
剩下可用的部件只能重制一個
There's only enough usable parts to rebuild one,
所以好好用
so use it wisely.
我也做了些改進
Made a few improvements, too.
如果你不能幫我們連上阿莉的代碼
None of which is gonna matter
這些都是百忙一場
if you can't get us access to Alie's code.
你操心夜之血脈的事
You worry about the Nightblood.
我來操心阿莉
I'll worry about Alie.
你怎麼能連上不存在這裡的代碼
How can you access code that doesn't exist here anymore?
我們已經有了計畫
We've got a plan.
我們還在等什麼
What are we waiting for?
我們出發吧
Let's move out.
小心
Be safe.
願我們再見
May we meet again.
保重
Good luck.
你可以的
You got this.
你說得對  他們要利用國王
You were right. They're using the king.
很好
Good.
那他們會親手把火種送來
Then they'll bring the flame right to us.
我們就守株待兔
And we'll be waiting.
到了  我們在這裡停
There it is. We stop here.
好  我們從這裡分開行動
All right. This is where we split up.
隧道的入口就在那裡
The entrance to the tunnel is right over there.
我們知道在哪
We know where it is.
我需要火種
I'm gonna need the flame.
我們的計畫只有在
Look. This only works
他們派安塔麗出來拿才能奏效
if they send Ontari out to get it.
如果他們沒看到  他們是不會那麼做的
If they don't see it, they won't do that,
捨不得孩子套不著狼
not much of a trap without the bait.
好
Fine...
我跟你一起去
But I'm coming with you.
不行  計畫並非如此
No way. That is not the plan.
現在改了
It is now.
我不會讓火種離開我的視線
I'm not letting that out of my sight...
而我也是唯一知道口令的人
And I'm the only one who knows the passphrase,
所以你可以告訴他們  沒有我
so you can tell them that without me,
安塔麗無法登位
Ontari can't ascend.
你要裝成是我的俘虜
You'll need to look like my prisoner.
好
Ok.
等一下  給我們一會兒
Wait a second. Give us a minute.
拜託  克拉克
Come on, Clarke.
你真的要拿自己的命冒險  相信那傢伙嗎
You're really willing to trust that guy with your life?
不
No...
但你會全程掩護我們
But you'll be covering us the entire time,
而我相信你
and I trust you.
挑個櫃子  雷文說應該在這裡
Pick a shelf. Raven said it would be here.
我們在找什麼來著
What are we looking for again?
一個帶內存的主板
A motherboard loaded with ram.
那應該像是
And that looks like--
一個帶內存的主板
A motherboard loaded with ram.
雷文說她需要一個處理能力很強的東西
Raven said she needs the processing power
來打開一扇通向阿莉的傳送門
to open a portal into Alie.
傳送門
Portal?
她是這麼叫的
That's what she calls it.
他想用阿莉的一塊芯片黑進去
She wants to use one of Alie's own chips to hack back in.
我們只需在把芯片放入安塔麗體內後
All we have to do is enter the kill code
輸入我們從火種中得到的刺殺命令
we get from the flame once we put it in Ontari.
遊戲就結束了
It's game over.
玩這一套呀
That old plan.
如果不成功呢
What if it doesn't work?
必須成功
It has to.
你和哈珀好了
So...you and Harper, huh?
我為你們高興
I'm happy for you.
怎麼  我不能為朋友感到高興
What, can't be happy for my friend?
你很長時間以來對任何事都不高興
You haven't been happy about anything in a long time.
沒錯  我的確沒高興過
You're right. I haven't been.
在韋瑟山發生的事改變了我
What happened in Mount Weather changed me.
我為之責怪所有人
I blamed everyone for it--
克拉克  你
Clarke, you.
我不再責怪了
I'm done blaming.
很高興你變回來了  兄弟
I'm glad you're back, brother.
我也是
Me, too.
等一下  就在那
Wait a second. There it is.
我們不能讓雷文建立傳送門
We can't let Raven build the portal.
找到了  我們走
We did it. Let's go.
把那給我
Give me that.
賈斯珀  我們需要那塊主板
Jasper, we need that motherboard.
雷文  快開門
Raven! Raven, open the door!
怎麼了
What's wrong?
蒙蒂  發生什麼了
Monty, what is it?
賈斯珀吞了芯片
Jasper's been chipped.
什麼  你確定嗎
What? Are you sure?
他刺傷了我
He stabbed me.
天啊
Oh, my god.
如果賈斯珀吞了芯片  阿莉就知道一切了
If Jasper's been chipped, then Alie knows everything.
對講機
Radio.
一號車  請回答
Rover one, come in.
見鬼  貝拉米快回答
Damn it, Bellamy, pick up.
信號沒有傳輸  設備壞了
It's not transmitting. It's not working.
讓我進去  蒙蒂
Let me in, Monty.
他們正走進陷阱
They're walking into a trap.
你的朋友最好就位了
Your friends better be in position.
快  快  我們走
Move, move, move. Come on. Let's go.
好的  走這邊
All right. This way.
這就是了
This is it.
把格柵打開
Get these grates open.
這一切結束後
When this is over,
安塔麗會知道是你幫了她
Ontari will know you helped her.
我向你保證
You have my word.
我們做好準備
Let's get ready.
我們的仗有打完的時候嗎
Are we ever gonna be done fighting?
當然了
Hell yes.
我們要在湖上建一座房子
We're gonna build a house on a lake...
而且你還要種玉米
And you're gonna plant corn.
還有養雞
And raise chickens.
是的
Yeah...
然後變老
And grow old.
十一點鐘方向
11 o'clock.
羅恩看見安塔麗後會發信號
Roan will signal when he sees Ontari.
我們等她站在他們身前
We wait until she's standing in front of them,
然後釋放瓦斯
and then we launch the gas.
他們會屏住呼吸
They're gonna be holding their breath,
所以我們動作要快
so we got to move fast.
人有點少啊
So much for the thousands of people.
對任何妨礙我們的人使用非致命武器
Anyone who gets in our way, we use nonlethal force.
這些人不是我們的敵人
These people are not the enemy.
他們被控制了
They're being controlled.
我們來這的唯一目標是干掉阿莉
The only thing we're here to kill is Alie.
-明白嗎  -明白
- Is that clear? - Clear.
-明白  -很好
- Clear. - Good.
我們開始吧
Here we go.
我是羅恩  阿茲哥達的國王
I am Roan, King of Azgeda...
我有司令想要的東西
And I have what the commander seeks.
我不喜歡這樣
I don't like what I'm sensing,
如果她想要  她可以出來找我
so if she wants it, she can come to me.
是亞哈
It's Jaha.
他在這幹什麼
What the hell is he doing here?
-看見安塔麗了嗎  -沒  穩住
- You see Ontari? - No. hold.
你好  克拉克
Hello, Clarke.
你母親見到你一定很高興
Your mother will be so pleased to see you.
你是誰  安塔麗在哪
Who are you? Where's Ontari?
她不會出來
Not coming out,
但你可以把火種交給我
but you can give the flame to me.
我確保交到她手裡
I'll be sure she gets it.
有些不對勁
Something's wrong.
在隧道里的朋友幫不了你
Your friends in the tunnel can't help you.
快把火種給我
Now give me the flame.
退後  否則她死
Back up, or she dies.
立即行動
Do it. Do it now.
跪下  放下武器
On your knees! Drop your weapon!
布萊克  靠牆
Blake, against the wall.
-放下  -轉過去
- Drop it. - Turn around!
別演了
Save the theatrics.
我們知道你們是一夥的  我們全知道了
We know you're together. We know everything.
那你應該知道她是唯一
Then you know she's the only one
可以激活火種
who can activate the flame.
你說得對
You're right.
我們得留著她
We need her alive.
快逃
Run.
但我們不用留你
But we don't need you.
不
No!
別碰我
No! No!
不要
No!
你還好嗎
You doing okay?
感覺還好
I think so.
要是刺中什麼重要器官
If it hit anything important,
我就完了吧
I wouldn't be, right?
是啊  你走運了
Right. You got lucky.
希望我們一直這麼走運
We could use some more of that.
哈珀一個在外面
Harper's out there alone.
哈珀是警衛  比你槍法準
Harper's a guard and a better shot than you.
她不知道賈斯珀吃了芯片
She doesn't know Jasper's chipped.
我知道  蒙蒂
I know that, Monty.
但我們不能冒險讓賈斯珀進來
We can't risk Jasper getting in here,
現在阿莉已經知道我想幹什麼了
not when Alie knows what I'm building.
雷文  計畫失敗了
Raven, the plan failed.
克拉克不能用無線電給我們代碼了
Clarke won't be radioing with the kill code.
我自己來找
I can find it myself.
如果生效  我就能殺了阿莉
If I can get this to work, I can kill Alie.
你之前試過了  沒有用
You tried this before. It didn't work.
我可以做到的  也必須做到
I can do it. I have to.
求你們了
Come on, guys.
讓我進去  我只想聊聊
Let me in. I just want to talk.
只要他還在這
As long as he's right here,
他就不會去找哈珀
he's not looking for Harper.
那就聊吧
So talk.
你聽起來沒事
You sound good.
我很高興
I'm glad.
我不想傷害你的  蒙蒂
I never want to hurt you, Msonty.
我不怪你  你受盡折磨
I don't blame you. You were tortured.
不  我沒有受到折磨
You got it wrong. I wasn't tortured.
沒錯  我是被打了幾頓
I mean, yeah, I was punched a couple of times,
但我並非為此吞下鑰匙
but that's not why I took the key.
你應該去看看露娜的船的  蒙蒂
You should've seen Luna's rig, Monty.
那裡很祥和  很安全
It was peaceful, safe.
大家都很幸福
The people were happy.
那有個叫夏伊的女孩
There was this girl there, Shay.
和她說話
When I was talking to her,
讓我自從到韋瑟山以來第一次認識到
I realized for the first time since mount weather,
我沒有在思念瑪雅
I wasn't thinking about Maya.
那裡很美  但被我們毀了
It was beautiful there, and we destroyed it.
不是我們  是阿莉干的
That wasn't us. It was Alie.
這不重要
It doesn't matter.
重要的是  阿莉
What matters is that Alie
可以驅散所有痛苦
can take away all that pain.
她可以為你做同樣的事
She can do the same for you.
開開門吧
Please open the door.
別讓雷文摧毀了我們的這一切
Don't let Raven ruin this for all of us.
你怎麼能這樣對我們
How could you do that to us?
我意識到了真相
I realized the truth.
他們把我們送到地表
They sent us all down here
來測試地表是否適宜生存
to see if the ground was survivable.
但在我看來  根本不適宜
From what I've seen, it's not.
放開我
Let me go.
我們很快就會放了你
You'll be free soon enough.
克拉克
Clarke...
我很想你
I've missed you.
我永遠不會吞下鑰匙
I won't take the chip ever.
現在
Right now,
我們只是需要你幫我們激發火種
we just need your help with the flame.
口令是什麼  克拉克
What's the passphrase, Clarke?
和她媽媽一樣頑固
Stubborn like her mother.
放開我
Let me go!
媽媽
Mom...
媽媽  別讓他們這樣對我
Mom, please don't let them do this.
我沒讓他們這樣對你
I'm not letting them do this.
我自己親手來
I'm doing it.
口令是什麼  克拉克
What's the passphrase, Clarke?
媽媽  這不是你自己
Mom, this isn't you.
我知道真正的你還在
I know you're in there.
求你了
Please.
口令是什麼
What's the passphrase?
不
No!
這都是可以停止的  克拉克
It can stop, Clarke.
只要把我們需要的告訴我們
Just tell us what we need to know.
我就說吧
I told you.
她的朋友們才是她的軟肋
Her friends are her weakness.
從貝拉米·布萊克開始
Start with Bellamy Blake.
我們走  她要的是貝拉米
Let's go. She wants Bellamy.
你們要帶他去哪
Where are you taking him?
別碰她
Leave her alone.
沒事的  小奧  沒事的
It's ok, O. It's ok.
我要是你  就趕緊趴在地上
You know, if I were you, I'd hit the deck.
墨菲  大家快趴下
Murphy? Everyone hit the ground!
閃亮登場
Fancy meeting you here.
很快會有人來了  我們得趕快
More will come. We have to hurry.
你沒事吧
You ok?
謝謝
Thank you.
你怎麼在這裡
What are you doing here?
不客氣
You're welcome.
內森  你看來不大好啊
Nathan, you've looked better.
而你挺好的
You haven't.
來
All right.
你和派克在一起
You're with Pike?
我們唯一能出去的辦法就是團結一致
Only way we get out of here is together.
他殺了林肯
He killed Lincoln--
逼他跪著
Put him on his knees,
一槍爆頭
shot him in the head.
因陀羅說得對
Indra's right.
我們需要每一個能戰鬥的戰士
We need every fighter we can get.
你們別磨磨蹭蹭了  快走吧
You guys missed the part where it's time to go?
我們不走
We're not leaving.
我們剛救了你們的命
We just saved your lives.
我好像突然有些後悔
Why do I think I'm gonna regret that?
克拉克有麻煩
Clarke is in trouble.
克拉克永遠都有麻煩
Clarke's always in trouble.
他們把她和火種帶進了塔裡
They took her and the flame to the tower.
這是確保安塔麗在那裡的籌碼
It's a safe bet Ontari's there, too.
我們阻止阿莉所需要的所有東西都在一個地方
Everything we need to stop Alie is in the same place.
如果我們上塔
If we go up that tower,
我們就沒辦法再出來了
we won't be able to fight our way out again.
但如果我們阻止了阿莉
If we stop Alie,
我們就不必了
we won't have to.
上塔  很好
Up the tower. Great.
除此之外也沒什麼別的可做了
You know, after this doing the right thing can kiss my ass.
我說過了  我們不能那麼做
Hey! I told you, that is not how we're doing this.
他們在擋路
They were in our way.
這些人不是我們的敵人
These people are not our enemy.
他們被阿莉控制了
They're being controlled by Alie,
我們可以救他們
and we can save them.
如果我們不行動  這樣的人就會多更多
There's gonna be a lot more of these people if we don't move.
我們繼續
Let's do this.
我來轉下來
I'll bring it down.
我們上去之後  你們燒掉電梯  然後爬上來
Once we're up, you blow the elevator and then climb.
毀掉身後的梯子  我去幹
Destroy the ladder behind us. On it.
拜託  你們明白這是自斷後路吧
Come on. You do realize we don't have a way down, right?
以後再困擾這個問題吧
A problem for another day.
我們走  電梯來了
Let's go. Our ride's here.
來嗎  小奧
Coming, O.?
如果這裡發生什麼事
If anything goes wrong down here,
他們會需要我幫忙
they'll need my help.
我們斷後
We got this.
推
Push.
你發現我們搞砸了吧
You get that we're screwed, right?
阿莉已經知道我們會來了
Alie already knows that we're coming.
計畫會奏效的
This plan will work.
你怎麼會在這
Why are you here?
我只是想活下去
I'm just trying to survive.
這裡不是只有你
You're not the only one here
想救自己在乎的人
trying to save someone you care about.
推
Push!
你為什麼那麼看著我
Why are you looking at me like that?
因為我知道你在想什麼
Because I know what you're thinking.
他怎麼還活著
Why is he still alive?
因為死人幫不上忙
Because the dead can't help us.
他曾是我的家
He was my home.
你的家
在這裡
不大好啊
Well, that's not good.
納特
Nate!
這不是你  凱恩  抱歉
This isn't you, Kane. I'm sorry.
他們要進來了
They're coming in.
他不會是一個人來的  我們得趕快
He won't be alone. We have to hurry.
布萊恩  你還好嗎
Bryan, you all right?
墨菲  準備好電棍
Murphy, get that baton ready.
電他  墨菲
Shock him, Murphy!
墨菲
Murphy!
快上電梯
Back on the wheel.
這裡  他們上電梯了
人快來了
We're about to have company.
想賭一把嗎
You want to bet?
我們要把走廊封上
We need to seal the corridor.
納特
Nate...
掩護
Take cover!
快來  墨菲
Come on, Murphy!
開槍  開槍  貝拉米
Shoot him! Shoot him! Bellamy!
謝了
Thank you.
她的朋友們很機智啊
Her friends are resourceful.
我們得即興發揮了
We'll have to improvise.
約翰·墨貝格  被割喉
John Mbege--sliced throat,
羅瑪·布萊格  胸部中矛
Roma Bragg-- spear to the chest,
沒我走運
not as lucky as me...
芬·柯林斯  死於克拉克之手
Finn Collins-- death by Clarke,
達克斯  死於克拉克之手  艾騰...
Dax--death by Clarke, Atom--
-這個應該能行  -酸霧
- This should do it. - Acid fog,
然後死於克拉克之手
then death by Clarke...
崔娜和帕斯卡
Trina and Pascal--
死了
Gone.
棒
Yes!
你進去了  起作用了
You're in. It worked.
我們還是得趕在阿莉發現之前
We still have to get the kill switch
拿到自殺口令
without Alie finding us.
康納和邁爾斯  因為墨菲塑膠窒息
Connor and Myles-- choked on plastic, thanks to Murphy.
德魯  臉中飛鏢
Drew--ninja star to the face.
是個好兆頭
That was a good one.
你們為什麼鎖門
Why'd you guys lock the door?
哈珀  你看到賈斯珀了嗎
Harper, do you see Jasper?
哈珀
Harper!
不要
Don't.
賈斯珀  如果你傷害她
Jasper, if you hurt her--
我知道你在乎她
I know you care about her.
你只要毀掉機器
All you have to do is destroy the machine,
她就沒事了  我保證
and she'll be fine, promise.
我可不希望你再失去任何人了
I don't want you to lose anyone else.
他們快到了  繼續推
They've got to be almost there. Keep pushing.
他們來了
They're coming.
各就各位
電梯一停下  我們就拿下他們
別怕  不是衝你來的
Don't be afraid. It's not for you.
不
No.
媽媽  媽媽  住手  聽我說
Mom, mom, stop. Listen to me.
我知道你能聽到我說話  住手
I know you can hear me. Just stop.
你知道該怎麼做
You know how to stop this.
等等  阿莉
Wait, Alie.
如果你殺了她  你永遠得不到你想要的
If you kill her, you'll never get what you want.
不是阿莉要殺我
Alie's not killing me.
是你
You are.
媽媽  求求你不要這麼做
Mom, don't do this, please.
我求求你  不要這麼做
I'm begging you, don't do it.
求求你
Please.
口令是什麼  克拉克
What's the passphrase, Clarke?
我不能  我不能說
I can't. I can't.
她會崩潰的
She'll break.
做吧
Do it.
不
No.
不  不
No! No.
不
No!
對不起
I'm so sorry.
他們到頂了
They're at the top.
我們走  我們設置好炸彈就跑
Let's go. We set the bomb and fly.
-三十秒  -我們走
- 30 seconds. - Let's go.
計時器設置好了  我們走
The timer's set. Let's move.
因陀羅
Indra.
凱恩  快回來
Kane, get back!
因陀羅
Indra!
他們在哪
待在這裡
他們到了
They're here.
我們不能讓他們得到你
We can't let them have you.
我明白
I understand.
你要做什麼  等等  住手
What are you doing? Wait. Stop.
亞哈  不要那麼做
Jaha, don't do this.
大殿往這邊走
Throne room's this way.
阿莉  住手  求求你住手
Alie, stop it. Please don't do this.
不
No!
對她大腦的損傷是永久的
Damage to her brain is substantial,
但她還會繼續活著
but she's still alive.
貝拉米  阻止他
Bellamy, stop him!
你還好嗎
Hey, are you ok?
她還活著嗎  她還有氣嗎
Is she alive? Is she breathing?
沒事  她還有氣
It's ok. She's breathing.
亞哈拿走了火種  去拿
Jaha has the flame. Get it.
我們不能讓安塔麗死
We can't let Ontari die.
我們得給她止血
We have to stop the bleeding.
-我拿到火種了  -她的脈搏很微弱
- I got the flame. - Her pulse is weak.
-至少她還活著  -來  按住傷口
- At least she's alive. - Here. Hold this to the wound.
我們要怎麼做
Come on. What are you gonna do?
我需要手電筒
I need a flashlight.
我們先取出芯片  然後把芯片放進去
First, we take out the chip. Then we put in the flame.
她的瞳孔毫無反應
Her pupils are unresponsive.
什麼  那是什麼意思
What? What does that mean?
-她腦死亡了  -她沒辦法給我們自殺代碼
- She's brain dead. - She can't give us the kill code.
完了
It's over.
我們被困在這裡了
We're trapped here.
未完待續
一大波正版授權“權力的遊戲”周邊向你靠近！
手機淘寶掃瞄左側二維碼
一起加入劇粉隊伍~
搜索微信公眾號
宅電舍動漫 有福利哦
特別鳴謝人人影視